

# ORPAA LUBEM IT SUPPORT OFFICER/MANAGER

Contact Details orpaastephen@gmail.com

+2347052532663

Contact Address:

Plot 208A, Hakimi Aliyu Layout, Mokwa, Niger State, 913104

Nationality:

Nigeria

Date of Birth:

18th October, 1996

Links

<u>Portfolio</u>

LinkedIn

Github

Twitter

#### > Skills

CCNA

\*\*\*

Windows Server

\*\*\*\*

Linux

\*\*\*\*

Flutter + Dart

\*\*\*\*

UI (Vue.js+HTML+CSS+JS)

\*\*\*\*

MS Office

\*\*\*\*

Fast Learner

\*\*\*\*

Adaptability

/taaprabiiii

\*\*\*\*

Communication Skills

## Profile

High-energy and dedicated IT Officer with accumulated experience assisting colleagues in analyzing and problem-solving technical issues with workable solutions. Forward-thinking and team-oriented with a proven history of thinking strategically and initiating action to meet deadlines. Recognized by management and colleagues as an individual who takes on challenges and new responsibilities, and gets things done right.

## **Employment History**

## Assistant IT Officer (Full-Time) at Flour Mills of Nigerian (Golden Sugar Company, Sunti)

Date: January, 2023 - Present

Key Responsibility:

- As an Assistant IT Officer I was involve providing technical support related to both hardware and software.
- Carryout quarterly system backup using Veeam
- Implement Cisco Security firewall on the Network
- Monitoring Network using Meraki dashboard and Ensuring smooth flow of internet on company Switches and Access points (Cisco Routers)
- Report and resolve network down times with full speed
- Responsible for update/implementation of system security patch, enforcing OS upgrade and Staff training for new UI usage
- Help to ensure the safe and efficient running of a company's IT gadgets and provide user technical support/assistance.
- Ensured company's computer network is always running smoothly, efficiently and up-todate
- Responsible for writing reports, training staff on new technologies, and developing/implement contingency plans in case of network failure.
- Performed installations and configuring computer on FMN Domain and Networks
- Setting up Peripherals, Maintaining and repairing them.
- And I analyzed several online job postings to identify these core duties and responsibilities to system end-users (staffs).

## User Support (Intern) at Federal University of Agriculture, Makurdi

Date: March, 2012 - September, 2013

Key Responsibility

- Assist over 3,000 students in the creation of student's Username and password to grant them access to ICT wireless facility
- Enable Staff to collate student data consumption information from the school admin network server.
- Team leader of IT student during the PC upgrade from wired to wireless card to enable wireless networking in ICT hall.
- Team leader for quarterly PC maintenance
- Assist Student use the school portal efficiently.

#### Junior Android Developer (Intern) at Build Space Hub

Date: March, 2021 - December, 2022

Key Responsibility

- Develop app using Flutter & Dart
- Implement Apps Using Firebase, Google Cloud and Google authentication
- Used Retrofit for handling RESTful AP calls
- Used Mobile-ads and Facebook



#### > Hobbies

Travelling
Writing Functional Codes

## > Languages

English - Professional

Hebrew - Basic Espanol - Basic Hausa - Fluent

#### > Education

Bachelor of Science (B.Sc)
 in Computer Science from
 Federal University of
 Agriculture, Makurdi
 August, 2023

 National Diploma from The Federal Polytechnic, Bida

Date: September, 2014

> SSCE from Government Day Seconder School, Kpege, Mokwa

Date: July, 2009

> FSLC from Abi Nursery and Primary School, Badariya Date: August, 2003 **↓** Computer Instructor (Full Time) at Rock Computer Cyber Café

Date: March, 2018 - March, 2021

Key Responsibility

- Install and Administrate Mikrotic software over the wireless network
- Configure/Setup wireless network firewall
- Used e-Platform (Remita, Quickteller, Others) for payment

## ♣ Computer Operator (Full Time) at Bekesoft InfoSys and DataTech

Date: November, 2009 - August, 2011

Key Responsibility

- Computer System Unit Assembly and Installation
- DBMS Application End-User
- MS-Office Application End-User
- Corel-Draw & CS-4 End-User

## ♣ Store Keeper (Full Time) at Saro Agro Science Company

Date: May, 2015 - March, 2018

Key Responsibility

- Monitor and ensure proper In-Flow and Out-Flow of Stocks ensure daily stock balancing with sales reps.
- Implemented new customer service strategies successfully, increasing customer satisfaction by 9% in 11 months.
- Calculate total payments received during a time period, and reconcile this with total sales.
- Used computerized systems that involve distributing and accounting for funds
- Operate POS cash register, handling 20 transactions on average daily
- Calculate total payments received during a time period, and reconcile this with total sales.
- Responsible for Quarterly Stock count and balancing of SKUs

### Security Personnel (Full Time) at Ashaka Security Company (ASCO)

Date: March, 2021 - December, 2021

Key Responsibility

Maintain total alertness and Secure all company properties within allocated perimeter

#### > Professional Certs

• Associate Android Developer at Google Developers

Date: May, 2021

Mobile-Web Specialist at Google Developers

Date: July, 2021

 Fundamental of Android & iOS App using Flutter & Dart at London App Brewery + Google Developers

Date: April, 2020

• CCNA Security at Network Bull, India

Date: September, 2020

• CCNA Networking (Routing & Switching) at Network Bull, India
Date: July, 2020

Diploma in Computer Operations at Bidapoly Consult

Diploma in Computer Operations at Bidapoly Consult
Date: August, 2012

#### References

...will be available on request.